

Carlos García

JOB TITLE

□ carlos.garcia@gnail.com

- +99 699999988
- **Q** London, England
- in linkedin.com/carlos-garcia

OBJECTIVE

Proactive individual with more than 2000 url's completed over 5 year in several IT departments. My experience is based in the development of highly complex web pages for private companies and publics institutions. My work quality is reflected as a finalist 5 times for the "ESANDI" awards, winning twice.

SKILLS

- Communication
- Phyton
- Java script
- Experiencie speaking at events

LANGUAGES

- English: fluent
- Spanish: native speaker
- French: beginner level

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB Developer - Inditex

2023 - Present

- Develop well-structured, maintainable code and thoroughly test your own work.
- Monitor ongoing performance of web applications and infrastructure online.
- Assist the Head of IT in assessing security of web applications and action requerid changes arising from 3rd party pen testing of systems.

WEB Developer - Penguin Random House

2020 - 2023

- Work within browser team to lead technical community.
- Engage with developers, for example on social media, in order to learn about their needs and gather feedback.
- Speak at and organise developer events both virtual and physical (travel will be a part of this role).

Database Administrator – Computer Center

2019 - 2020

- Work within browser team to lead technical community.
- Engage with developers, for example on social media, in order to learn about their needs and gather feedback.

EDUCATION

WEB Development MASTER'S - University of Liverpool 2011 – 2013

Computer Engeeniring DEGREE – Keele University 2007 - 2010

REFERENCES

Andrés PRYM

Director

INDITEX Textile Design Industry 135 Heygate St, London, England +999 9999 9999 andres.prym@gnail.com

Sara COOPER

Head of HR Resources
PENGUIN RANDOM HOUSE
Garden Row, London, England
+999 9999 9999
sara.cooper@gnail.com

Estimado (a) Candidato (a),

Aumenta tus posibilidades de conseguir trabajo rápidamente al **descargar nuestro kit de empleo** que contiene todas las herramientas que te ayudarán a lograr tus objetivos.

→ Descarga tu kit gratis aquí: https://www.modelos-de-curriculum.com/descargar-kit/

Además, lee nuestros artículos, te permitirán conseguir el trabajo ideal:

- Cómo Hacer un Currículum en Inglés
- Preguntas Frecuentes en una Entrevista de Trabajo en Inglés
- Cómo Preparar una Entrevista de Trabajo en Inglés
- Cómo Hacer un Currículum en PDF
- + Ejemplos de Curriculum Vitae Gratis

¡Que no se te escape! Acompaña tu currículum con una <u>carta de presentación</u> para impactar aún más a los reclutadores.

- Ejemplo de carta de presentación en inglés
- Cómo Hacer una Carta de Presentación
- Ejemplos de Carta de Presentación
- Plantillas de Carta de Presentación

COPYRIGHT - POR FAVOR LEER ESTE MENSAJE

© Estos ejemplos de modelos de currículum gratuitos son propiedad de Azurius S.L. Puede descargarlos y modificarlos sin ningún problema, siempre y cuando sea para su uso personal.

No olvides quitar este aviso de copyright antes de modificar e imprimir tu CV.

No se puede revender estos ejemplos ni sus derivados. No puedes ponerlos a disposición en otros sitios web sin nuestro consentimiento. Para cualquier pregunta relacionada, escríbenos a contacto@modelosdecurriculum.com